Now, pretty much everyone has a camera in their back pocket – in the form of a smartphone.
如今，几乎每个人的后口袋里都有一台相机——以智能手机的形式。
It's easy to take hundreds of photos without needing to really consider set up or storage.
人们可以轻松拍摄数百张照片，而无需真正考虑设置或存储。
And it's very hard to imagine that, at one time, capturing an image was an almost impossible process.
很难想象，曾几何时，捕捉影像是一个几乎不可能完成的程序。
Going back even before traditional film cameras, there were camera obscuras.
回溯到传统胶片相机之前，暗箱此时出现。
These were boxes with a small hole in them.
暗箱是带有小孔的盒子。
Through one side, an image could be projected onto a wall on the opposite side of the box.
通过一侧，影像可以投射到盒子另一侧的墙壁上。
However, the picture was upside down, very faint, and couldn't be captured in physical form – a bit like the images we see on modern projectors.
然而，图像是倒立的，非常模糊，且无法以物理形式保存——有点像我们在现代投影仪上看到的影像。
In 1839, a French artist managed to work out a way to store and save photographs.
1839年，一位法国艺术家成功找到了一种存储和保存照片的方法。
He projected the image onto a shiny metal plate treated with chemicals.
他将影像投射到经过化学处理的闪亮金属板上。
These images were in black and white.
这些图像是黑白的。
The first colour photo ever taken was of a tartan ribbon.
有史以来第一张彩色照片拍摄的是一条格子呢丝带。
The image was composed of three black and white photographs, each taken through a red, blue or green filter.
这张图像由三张黑白照片合成，每张分别通过红色、蓝色或绿色滤镜拍摄。
So, how did we get from these early photographs to the kind we put into a frame and keep?
那么，我们是如何从这些早期照片发展到如今放入相框中珍藏的那种照片的呢？
Before the digital revolution, an image was captured on a negative, and this method is still chosen by some photographers today.
在数字革命之前，影像被记录在底片上，这种拍摄方法至今仍被一些摄影师采用。
A negative is an inverted image on a small strip of glass or plastic film which can then be exposed to light and processed onto photographic paper.
底片是玻璃或塑料胶片小条上的倒像，然后可以曝光并冲洗到相纸上。
When this was the main source of obtaining physical copies of photographs, it was a lengthy process with customers having to take the negatives to a shop and wait for their pictures to be developed.
当这是获得照片实体副本的主要方式时，这是一个漫长的过程，顾客需要将底片带到商店，等待照片被冲洗出来。
That was until digital photography came along in the 70s.
直到20世纪70年代数码摄影出现。
Digital cameras captured images that could be saved as files and manipulated on a computer.
数码相机拍摄的影像可以保存为文件，并在电脑上进行处理。
Those are the kind of photos we take today on our phones.
这就是我们今天用手机拍摄的那种照片。
So, don't take the camera in your pocket for granted.
所以，不要把你口袋里的相机视为理所当然。
It's been years in the making.
它经历了多年的发展才得以问世。